我来了
Hi,you guys.
怎么了？
What's the matter?
又是那种很讨厌的状况
Well,it's just.. It's one of these situations that I just hate.
有一个按摩的客人给我三张票 去摩根却斯博物馆看展览
A massage client gave me three tickets...to the Helmut Peltz Exhibit at the Morgan Chase Museum.
你觉得你得跟他上床
Now you're thinking you gotta sleep with him.
不是，他给我三张票 但是我们有六个人
No. No. It's just that he gave me three tickets and there are six of us.
我弃权 我也是
-I'll give up my ticket. -Me too.
你们真大方 罗斯应该也很大方
Okay. That's so generous.And I think Ross is generous too.
太好了，那我们女生自己去 太好了
Great! Then it's just us girls.Great.Yeah.
是什么展览？
So what is the exhibit?
主要是女同志性爱摄影展 还可以打电动，吃免费三明治
It's mostly just photographs...of lesbian love scenes interspersed with video games and free sandwiches.
讨厌啦
Oh,man!
罗斯，钱德说你周末 不想去女同志三明治博物馆
Hey,Ross,listen.Chandler got you out of going to the lesbian sandwich museum this weekend.
谢谢，我有节目了 伊丽莎白和我要出城去
Thanks,but I have plans. Elizabeth and I are going out of town.
太好了，你能赚不少钱呢
-That's great! -Yeah.Think about all the money that you're gonna make.
什么意思？
Why? What?
是她爸找你去当保姆对吧？
Well,her father pays you for babysitting,right?
真好笑，但你们也该有所长进 别再闹了
That's funny. But maybe it's time to move on.You know,let it go. Stop it!
况且瑞秋在和她爸交往 而他比她大多了
Besides,Rachel's going out with Elizabeth's father...so he's much older than she is.
看来不只是我对化石有兴趣
Looks like I'm not the only one interested in fossils.
这话只会提醒我们 你对化石有兴趣
All that does is remind us that you're interested in fossils.
好吧，瑞秋想和他甜言蜜语 必须很大声说，否则他听不清
Okay,okay.Rachel's gonna need to yell sweet nothings in his ear.
罗斯 拜托，这句很好笑啊
-Ross? -Come on! That's funny.
因为他戴助听器，因为…
Because he's gonna.. He's got,like,a hearing aid.
因为他很老
Because he's all old.
失陪一下
One second.
听着，罗斯
Okay,look,Ross.
因为丽莎很喜欢你 我决定接受你们交往的事
Just so you know,since Lizzie likes you so much...I've accepted the fact that you're dating her.
真的？太好了 是啊
Really? That's great.
但后来我又反悔了 我就是这么善变
Yeah,but then I changed my mind.I'm funny like that.
我已经告诉她，现在我告诉你 我不希望你再和我女儿见面
So I told Lizzie,now I'm telling you.I don't want you seeing my daughter anymore.
好，我知道你很不高兴 没错
Look,I realize it upsets you.Yes,it does.
但伊丽莎白和我都是成年人
But Elizabeth and I are both adults...
所以你也拿我们没办法
so I don't think there's anything you can do about it.
我会告诉学校你们在交往 让你被开除
I'll tell the university about your relationship and have you fired.
有备而来喔
Oh,a man with a plan!
本集播出：“保罗很男人”
The One Where Paul's The Man
主演：珍妮佛安妮斯顿
寇妮考克斯阿奎特
丽莎库卓
麦特勒布兰
马修派瑞
大卫修蒙
好兴奋喔 你的照片又要重回名人墙了
This is so exciting. You can get your picture back up on the wall of fame.
就是啊，这里什么大明星都有
He's got all the big actors.
之前在墙上时好快乐
It was so cool when I was up there.
我经常和吉姆贝路西说笑
Me and Jim Belushi would just be cracking up about something.
后来我被“我们的日子”开除 照片被拿下来
I get fired off Days of Our Lives and he takes me down.
现在他在嘲笑我
Now he's just laughing at me.
你看那个自鸣得意的混蛋
Look at him. That smug Belushi bastard!
也许你可以挂在麦特劳尔旁边
Okay. Maybe when they put your picture back up they could put you by Matt Lauer.
你看他在对我微笑
Look at him just smiling at me.
我知道，我们很配
Yeah,I know. We'd be great together.
我回来了 你是谁？
-So I'm back. -Who are you?
乔伊崔比亚尼，我之前上过墙
Joey Tribbiani.From the wall?
也许这样你会想起来
Okay,maybe this will jog your memory.
总之，我可以回墙上了 我主演了一出新戏
Okay,anyway.I'm ready to go back up on the wall. I'm the star of a new TV show.
哪一出？指给我看
-Show me in the TV book.
还没上档 那你就还不能上墙
-It's not on TV yet.Well,then it's not on the wall yet.
好吧，我拿录影带给你看
Okay,fine. I will bring you a tape.
你手边有麦特劳尔的衣服吗？ 还没洗过的？
So,now,do you have any of Matt Lauer's clothes?Maybe? Just ones that haven't been cleaned yet?
我好喜欢来博物馆 接受文化熏陶 是的
I love museums.Soaking up all the culture. -Yeah.
要先去哪里？
-Where do you want to start?
礼品贩卖部 也对
-The gift shop!
然后去吃饭
-And then lunch.
好，但我不能吃太多 保罗今晚要带我去吃饭
-Yes,but I can't eat too much.Paul's taking me out to dinner tonight.
他说会有个大惊喜
He said he has a big surprise planned.
他会不会要告诉你他是同性恋？
Do you think maybe he's gonna tell you he's gay?
什么？为什么？
What? No,why?
不为什么，那样真的会很惊喜
No reason. That would just be a really big surprise,right?
红毯可以铺在这边 然后在这边证婚
You could put the aisle over here and have the wedding ceremony over here.
原来这里可以结婚 这里当礼堂的确很美
I didn't know you could get married here.This would be a beautiful place to get married.
但我不会把红毯铺在那边 更不会在那边证婚
But I wouldn't put the aisle there. And I would never have the ceremony there.
应该在这个漂亮的拱门下证婚
You'd have the ceremony under a beautiful arch.
有什么事吗？
May I help you?
抱歉打断你 这里很美，经常举办婚礼吗？
Sorry. Didn't mean to interrupt. It's just such a beautiful space.Do you do a lot of weddings?
是的，这里很受欢迎 预约已经排到2年后，抱歉
-Yes,we're popular.There's a two-year waiting list. Sorry.
莫妮卡，你也应该去预约
Monica,you should put your name down for this place.
什么？你疯了吗？ 我又不结婚，我甚至还没订婚
What? Are you crazy?I'm not getting married. I'm not even engaged.
但还要等2年
But there's a two-year wait.
要是你2年后订了婚 还得再等2年，那就4年了
What if you get engaged in two years?Then you've got to wait another two years?That's four years.
钱德才不会等那么久 他会去找别人
Chandler's not gonna wait that long.He's gonna find somebody else.
某个有在这里预约的人
Someone who did put their name on the list.
先预约又不会怎样
It can't hurt to put your name down.
要是2年后没订婚就放弃不用
If,in two years,you're not engaged,you just don't use it.
先预约的确不会怎样
I guess there is no harm in putting my name down.
我也要预约 我也要
I'm gonna do it too.Me too!
真的？你要嫁给谁？
-Really? Who would you marry?
我不知道，我现在还没有对象
-I don't have anyone right now.
菲比
Oh,Phoebe.
别为我难过 至少我的男朋友不是同性恋
Don't feel too sorry for me. At least my boyfriend isn't gay.
菲比，你根本… 别逼我批评你的那个
Phoebe,that's not..Don't even get me started on yours.
你看过录影带了吗？ 看过了
-Did you watch the tape of my show? -I did.
好，让我回墙上吧
-Let's get me back up there.
不行，你不能上墙
-You don't go up on the wall.
但你看过我的戏了
-What? But you saw the show.
对，它冒犯了我的同胞
-lt was very offensive to my people.
干洗店老板吗？
Dry cleaners?
俄国人 它把他们演成恐怖分子和坏蛋
Russians. It showed them as terrorists and villains.
好，你看，你把哈里森福特挂在这
Okay,okay. Look,you got Harrison Ford up there!
没错，福特先生是个好顾客 他带很多衣服来，你两手空空
That's right. Mr. Ford is a very good customer.He brings us a lot of clothes. You bring nothing!
或许吧，但在《空军一号》里
Okay,that may be true.But in Air Force One,
俄国人是恐怖分子，很邪恶
okay,the Russians were terrorists and evil!
他还杀了一堆俄国人 那样很冒犯你们
And plus,he kills a bunch of them. That's offensive to Russians.
我没看过
-I've never seen it.
你应该要看，很精彩
-You should. It's great!
这里真的好漂亮
This place is really beautiful.
对啊，我从小就常来 这里以前是我奶奶家
I've been coming here since I was a kid. This used to be my grandma's.
我只遗传了我奶奶的眼睛
The only thing I got from my grandmother was her eyes.
我不是说她的眼珠子
I mean,not her actual eyeballs.
大家都说我的眼睛…
But people say that my eyes look...
要不要亲热？ 好啊
Do you wanna make out?Sure.
你还好吗？怎么了？
Are you okay?What's wrong?
我只是想到你爸爸
Yeah. I was just thinking about your father.
只要你能兴奋就好
Well,whatever works for you.
不是，他有点把我吓到了
No.He just really freaked me out before.
我们得再多瞒着一个人 那又怎样
So we have to hide our relationship from one more person.Big deal.
况且我们一直很乐在其中 没错
Besides,we've had fun hiding it.Yeah.
你有准备防护措施吗？
-Yeah? -You brought protection,right?
怎么了？这里有熊吗？
Why,are there,like,bears or something?
你是说那个，没有，我忘了
Protection. Yeah. No,yeah. That.. That I forgot.
我居然带了两瓶防蚊液 却忘了带那个
I can't believe I brought two cans of bug spray and forgot that.
那我去买
-I'll run to the store and get some.
不，我是男人，我去买
-I'm the guy. I'll get it.
你知道商店在哪里吗？ 不知道
-Do you know where the store is? -No.
你想骑粉红脚踏车逛大街吗？
Do you wanna ride around town on my little pink bicycle?
有点想
A little bit.
我10分钟后回来 好
I'll be back in 10 minutes.
你先进浴缸里等我 好
Get in the hot tub and I'll meet you there.Okay.
天哪，好棒的惊喜 这栋房子好漂亮
Oh,my God! What a great surprise! This is such a beautiful house!
谢谢，这是我妈的房子 这里是厨房
Thank you. It used to be my mother's. This is the kitchen.
钱德 乔伊
-Hey,Chandler. -Hey,Joe.
人总得找点事情做
Everybody's gotta be doing something.
这里是莫妮卡和钱德的家
You've reached Monica and Chandler's.
如果你听到这则留言 我们可能在筛选电话
If you're listening to this message,we're probably screening.
就是
Yeah,we are.
我是摩根却斯博物馆的海蒂 我要找莫妮卡盖勒
Hi,this is Hildy from the Morgan Chase Museum.I'm calling for Monica Geller.
有人取消预约 如果她还想在我们这里举行宾和盖勒的婚礼
I wanted to let her know that there was a cancellation.If she's still interested in having the Bing-Geller wedding in our facility...
现在有空了
...it is available..
我是钱德宾，我是钱德宾
This is Chandler Bing! This is Chandler Bing!
是的，我是新O
Yes,the groom.
不，我不是
No,not the groom!
这里好幽静
It's so secluded up here.
我知道，所以我喜欢这里
I know. That's why I like it here.
全世界好像只剩我们两个人
I feel like we're the only two people in the world.
抱歉
Sorry.
怎么了？你看到老鼠了吗？
What's the matter,honey?Did you see a little mouse?
不是，大熊，外面有大熊 你要不要…要不要去看一下？
No! Big bear! Big bear outside!I think I..Actually,would you go check on that?
亲爱的，这里没有熊
We don't have any bears here.
好吧，帮我倒杯健怡可乐好吗
Well,okay.Would you get me a Diet Coke?
好，我马上回来 好
-Okay. Be right back. -Okay.
你在这里干嘛？ 你又在这里干嘛？
-What are you doing here? -What are you doing here?
我是跟保罗来的 我认出他的脚踝了
-I came with Paul! -Yeah. I recognized the ankles.
伊丽莎白呢？ 她去买东西
-Where is Elizabeth? -She's at the store.
你让女生去买东西？ 我知道商店在哪里吗？
-You make the girl go to the store? -Do I know where the store is?
快出来
Hurry up. Get out.
拿来了，亲爱的
Here you go,honey.
谢谢你 健怡可乐
-Thank you! -Diet Coke.
冰块，我要冰块
Ice.I need ice.
好
Okay.
谢谢你 我马上回来
-Thank you. -Be right back.Okay.
又是冰块这一招
You and your ice.
出来，快点
Get out! Get out! Go! Come on!
不行，他在那里面
No,not in there! Not in there! He's in there!
你真的听到熊叫了吗？ 进去啦
-Did you really hear a bear? -Go!
来了
Here you go,honey.
一杯加冰的健怡可乐
One Diet Coke with ice.
谢谢
Thank you.
真高兴有你在
I am so happy that you're here.
我回来了 伊丽莎白
-Here I am! -Elizabeth!
看，伊丽莎白来了
Look! Elizabeth's here!
你在跟谁说话？ 你们啊
Who were you talking to?You guys?
你怎么知道我们在这里？
How did you know we were here?
她一定是看到往车库的方向 有轮胎印
She obviously saw the tire tracks leading up to the closed garage.
是啊
Obviously.
伊丽莎白，你来这里干什么？
What are you doing here?
你是来这里写学期论文的吗？
Did you come up here to work on that term paper or something?
没错
Yeah.
那你去那个房间写吧
Well,why don't you go in that room and do your homework?
我不会去那个房间写 那是我爸的卧房
I wouldn't do it in there. That's my dad's bedroom.
那是你爸的卧房
That's your dad's bedroom.
That's your dad's bedroom!
你干嘛这么大声？
Why are you yelling?
这杯健怡可乐让我好兴奋
That Diet Coke,I think,just straight to my head!
亲爱的
Hi,honey.
待会儿见
See you later.
我买了东西要帮你煮晚餐
Wait. I bought groceries. I was gonna make you dinner.
下次先问我
Well,next time,ask!
或者至少等我先开口
Or at least wait for me to ask!
我是摩根却斯博物馆的海蒂
Hi,this is Hildy from the Morgan Chase Museum.
我要找莫妮卡盖勒 完了
-I'm calling for Monica Geller. -Oh,no.
有人取消预约 如果她还想在我们这里办宾和盖勒的婚礼
I wanted to let her know that there was a cancellation.If she's still interested in having the Bing-Geller wedding in our facility...
现在有空了 拜托，他没听到，他没听到
it is available....Please. He didn't hear it!
我是钱德宾，我是钱德宾
This is Chandler Bing! This is Chandler Bing!
不！
No!
有什么事吗？
Can I help you?
决定谁能上墙的那个人呢？
Yeah,where's the guy who decides whose pictures go up on the wall?
他现在不在 不会吧
-He's not here right now. -You're kidding me!
记得告诉他 乔伊崔比亚尼带了一堆衣服来
Make sure you tell him that Joey Tribbiani stopped by to drop off all these clothes.
我是个演员 我想让我的照片上墙
I'm an actor. I'm trying to get my picture on the wall.
其实有两个人能决定这件事
You know,there are two people who could get your picture up there.
是吗？
Oh,really?
也许我们应该去喝一杯
Well,maybe you and I go out for drinks.
你是另外一个没错吧？
You're the other one,right?
丽莎，你今晚要留下来吗？
So,Lizzie,are you planning on staying the night?
不，我要尽快离开
No,no. Believe me,I'm leaving as soon as possible.
那好…不是我们不要你留下来。很明显我们欢迎你
Good. Not that we don't want you to stay. Obviously,you're welcome.
你还有多少功课？
How much more homework do you have?
只剩一个问题不知道怎么解决
I just have one problem left that I do not know how to solve.
瑞秋，也许你可以上楼来帮我
Rachel,maybe you wanna come upstairs and help me figure it out?
是吗？
Really?
好，我上楼 你去车上帮我拿东西
Okay,I'll go upstairs...if you get me something from the car.
你要拿什么东西？
What do you need from the car?
给我惊喜啊
Surprise me.
好
Okay.
你要去车上，我要去楼上 这就是目前的状况
So you're gonna be in the car! I will be upstairs!That's where everybody's gonna be!
放轻松，放轻松 你表现得很好
Just relax. Relax,Paul. You're doing great.
她喜欢你，她…她喜欢你
She likes you.I think she likes you. She likes you.
知道为什么吗？因为你是个纯爷们
You know why? Because you're a neat guy.
你是男子汉，你是男子汉
You are the man.You are the man!
还是很有料，很性感
Still got it.Still sexy.
你是个爱情机器
You're just a love machine.
我是个爱情机器 我只为你服务，宝贝
I'm just a love machine and I won't work for nobody but you! Hey
上场了
Showtime.
我是个爱情机器，宝贝
I'm just a love machine,yeah baby
菲比，你有见到钱德吗？ 没有，怎么了？
-Phoebe? -Yeah?-Have you seen Chandler? -No,why?
博物馆那个女人打电话来说 有人取消预约
The museum called and said that there was a cancellation...
我们可以提前举行婚礼 结果钱德听见了
and that we could move up our wedding. And Chandler heard.
就是啊，你觉得有多严重？
I know. How bad is this?
对一般男人来说很严重 但是对钱德…我的天哪
Well,with a regular guy,it's bad. With Chandler,oh,dear God!
我知道，他被吓到了 我到处都找不到他
I know! And he totally freaked out. I can't find him anywhere!
你要怎么办？ 反正我再也不听你的话了
-What are you gonna do? -I'm never going to listen to you again.
“先预约又不会怎样”
"What harm can it do if you put your name down?"
那是瑞秋说的 瑞秋不在这里
-Rachel said that. -Well,Rachel's not here!
她真的已经把你挂上去了？
You really think she put your picture up already?
这是什么话？
Did she put my picture up?
开玩笑，约会完之后 她就算挂十张我都不会惊讶
You kidding,after the date we had?I wouldn't be surprised if she put 10 of my pictures up there.
只不过我只给了她一张 不知道她要去哪里再弄九张
Except for the fact that I only gave her one. I don't know where she'd get the other nine.
在这里
Here it is!
乔伊，你为什么要签“混蛋”
Joey,why did you sign it "son of a bitch"?
我没有啊，这是谁干的？
-I didn't do that. Who would do that?
混蛋 问他好了
-Son of a bitch!Okay. Maybe ask this guy.
你，滚出我的店
-You! Get out of my shop!
他做了什么？ 他跟我老婆约会
-What did he do?-He went out with my wife!
乔伊
-Joey!
我没有跟你老婆约会，好吗？ 我是跟她约会
I did not go out with your wife! Okay?I went out with her.
她就是我老婆
That's my wife!
我指的不是她，我指的是她
I'm not pointing at her,no. I'm pointing at her.
赛妲麦默瑞
"Zelda McMurray."
她是谁啊？她凭什么上墙？   快滚
Who the hell..? How did she get up there?!Get out!
我们还是走好了
-Well,we should go. -Yeah.
罗斯？罗斯？
Ross?
伊丽莎白
Elizabeth!
好，我从窗户爬出去
Okay. I'm gonna go out this window.
我们前门见，你就说你要回家 好
I'll meet you at the front door. Tell them you're going home.-Okay.
等等，别进去，我还要喝汽水
-Wait! No,don't go in there!Don't go in there! I need another soda!
罗斯
Ross!
天哪，罗斯，你在这里干什么
Oh,my God,Ross! What in heaven's name are you doing here?
所以我们不能再见面了
And that is why we cannot see each other anymore.
罗斯，我们得好好谈一谈
Ross,you and I are gonna have to have a little talk.
爸 接着就是你
-Daddy,I.. -You're next!
好，我不知道他在这里
Okay. I didn't know he was here.
让我把话问清楚
Let me just see if I got this straight.
我叫你离我女儿远一点 否则就让你被开除
I tell you to stay away from my daughter or I'll have you fired.
结果你听到的是
What you heard was: "Take my daughter...
“带我女儿到我乡下的别墅” “破坏我和瑞秋的周末”
come up to my country house and ruin my weekend with Rachel."
拜托，你听我说
-Please,Paul. Just let me explain.
不，你听我说：开除
-No! Let me explain! Fired!
好，开除就开除
Okay,fine. Fine. Have me fired.
我只想你知道 我们也没那么不同 我的意思是
But I want you to know...that you and I are not all that different. I mean...
我也是个纯爷们
I,too,am a "neat guy."
什么？
What?
我也是个爱情机器
And I,too...am "just a love machine."
罗斯…
Ross
我带你去客房看看  好
-Let me show you the guest room. -Okay.
对不起，你别再害怕了
I'm so sorry. Please stop freaking out.
我没有害怕啊
I'm not freaking out.
我干嘛害怕？
Why would I?
有个叫海蒂的说我们要结婚了 这是常有的事
A woman named Hildy called and said we were getting married.But that happens every day.
亲爱的，那个地方很漂亮
Honey,we were at this beautiful place...
我只是预约好玩的，会怎样吗
and I just put our names down for fun.I mean,what's the harm in that?
会这样
-Right here.
钱德，你千万别以为我想给你压力
Please don't think I was trying to pressure you.
菲比和瑞秋觉得… 菲比和瑞秋
-Phoebe and Rachel thought.. -Phoebe and Rachel?
所以比我早知道我们要结婚的 有你，菲比和瑞秋
So the people that knew about our wedding before me were you...Phoebe and Rachel,
海蒂和一个叫星光魔力的乐团
Hildy,and some band called the Starlight Magic Seven...
对了，他们也有空
who are available,by the way.
我错了，我完全没有那个意思
It was a mistake.Please don't take this to mean anything,because it doesn't.
好吧
Okay.
真的？
Really?
如果你真的没有那个意思 你知道我还没准备好
Yes. If it really doesn't mean anything,because you know I'm not ready.
我知道，我知道 好
I know.I know.Okay.
我去告诉乔伊你回来了 我们刚才好担心
All right.I'm gonna go tell Joey that you're back.We were really worried about you.
不是叫了卷饼没送来吗？ 他以为跟那件事有关
And that guy that never delivered his burrito?He thought there was some sort of connection.
她相信了吗？ 相信了
Did she buy it?Totally.
海蒂有带你参观吗？ 有，那里好漂亮
-So did Hildy show you the place? -Yeah. It's beautiful.
你居然要跟莫妮卡求婚了 就是啊
I can't believe you're gonna ask Monica to marry you.I know.
甘瑟
-Hey,Gunther.
把这些卡布奇诺端到11桌 那个男的要意大利脆棒
-Take these cappuccinos to table 11.And that guy wants some biscotti.
我只是要一杯咖啡
I just actually came in for a cup of coffee.
你还在这里打工吗？
Do you still work here?
没有，我早就不做了
No. I quit a long time ago.
我没有告诉你吗？抱歉
Did I forget to tell you that? I'm sorry.
反正我也打算开除你 太好了
-Cool. I was gonna fire you anyway. -Great!